人人影視傾情奉獻
翻譯  ET外星人
翻譯  沫沫
翻譯  TheWalkingNerd
翻譯  江湖人稱王姑娘
翻譯  國士章魚X
翻譯  杏仁斯嘉麗
時間軸  壬虛浪影
顧問  老杜
后期  餓得慌
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第四季  第十二集
否則  這就是社會主義
Otherwise, it was just socialism,
那是注定要失敗的
which is built to fail.
失敗是不會為你加分的  總統先生
And you don't get points for failure, Mr. President.
人們不想要失敗  他們要的是成功
People don't want failure. They want success.
想要
成功
那就討論一下最近的功績吧
Let's discuss our recent success then.
那就
討論
一下
最近的
成績
你一直指責總統
You have been very critical of the president
對恐怖活動的態度不夠強硬
for not being strong on terror.
就在上周  特種部隊逮捕了尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪
Just last week, U.S. Special forces captured Yusuf Al Ahmadi,
并把他收監入獄
and they have him in custody.
那么你現在會不會說
So would you now say that
你對總統的指責是毫無根據的呢
your criticism of the president was unfounded?
對艾哈邁迪的逮捕是一個進步
The capture of Ahmadi is a step forward,
但真正的問題是長久的安全
but the real issue here is sustained security.
總統沒跟敘利亞人打招呼
The president sent in American troops
就派出了美國軍隊
without consulting the Syrians.
那對我們日后與他們的合作
Now, that's gonna do real damage to our ability
將造成很大傷害
to work with them in the future.
2016總統與副總統競選辯論
重點不在于建功立業
See, this isn't about notches in a belt.
而是給我們國家以更安全的世界環境
It's about a safer world for our nation.
給我們的孩子一個更好的未來
A better future for our children.
州長  我明白"安全""孩子"等字眼
Governor, I understand that words like "safer"
有很好的效果
and "children" play well.
但國家安全是一個復雜且千變萬化的領域
But national security is a complex and ever-changing landscape
有時也需要約束
that sometimes requires restraint,
有時也需要果斷的行動
sometimes decisive action.
所以我覺得我們最好
So I think maybe we want to
放下眼前聽起來不錯的詞
put aside what sounds good in the moment
現實一點討論適合我們的政策
and be adaptable with our policy in terms of reality.
我不需要人教我什么是現實
Oh, I don't need a lecture on reality
好像我還是小男生似的  安德伍德夫人
like I'm a schoolboy, Mrs. Underwood.
我真正在中東打過仗
I've actually fought in the Middle East.
將軍也是
So has the general.
我們對國際外交的觀點并不只是花言巧語
Our views on international diplomacy aren't just pretty words.
我們可以如你所愿討論政策  州長
We can debate policy all you'd like, Governor,
但有一件事不容置疑
but there is one thing that is undebatable.
那就是沒有了領袖的哈里發國
And that is ICO is no longer the threat it once was
威脅性已不比從前
without their leadership.
你不看辯論嗎
You're not watching the debate?
我知道他們要說什么
I know what they're going to say.
我能幫你什么  道格
How can I help you, Doug?
我告訴過你會有這么一天的
I told you there'd be a day.
你完全可以帶著這些光榮退休
There's no reason you shouldn't keep this and retire with honor.
情況如何
How are we looking?
"千變萬化"很有沖擊力
Yeah, high impact on "ever-changing."
康威上鉤了
And Conway took the bait
連"小男生"和"花言巧語"都出來了
and played right into "schoolboy" and "pretty",
合起來就是"可愛男生"  太美妙了
which gives you "pretty boy." It was beautiful.
婚姻的事怎么樣
What about the marriage stuff?
他們越是反復在任何語境中
Well, the more they can keep saying
說"一起"  "超越"
"together" and "beyond" and "become"
和"成為"  我們都加分
in any context, we score on those.
我不會跟你討論
I don't discuss the private conversations
我們情報委員會的私下談話
we have on the Intelligence Committee.
告密會讓你孤立無援
Whistle-blowing insulates you.
那就給我黨提名人拆臺嗎
And kneecap my party's nominee?
休想
I don't think so.
他會在這次辯論中說謊
He's going to lie about it at this debate.
他們都會
They both are.
你只是說出真相
You're going to tell the truth.
你不能二者兼得  州長
You can't have it both ways, Governor.
我們抓到他了  結束
We got him, period.
這是單方面  目光短淺的行為
Unilateral, short-sighted action.
單方面是因為你和將軍
Unilateral because you and the general
讓共和黨就跟俄羅斯人合作的事反對我
pitted the Republicans against my involving the Russians.
那是無稽之談
That's just not true.
你是說你沒有
Are you saying that you did not
讓將軍跟眾議院情報委員會的人聯系嗎
have the general contact members of the House Intelligence Committee?
將軍  你愿意評論一下嗎
General, would you care to comment?
我辭去職務后
When I resigned my commission,
就不再跟國會的人
I stopped talking to members of Congress
談論國家安全事宜了
about matters of national security.
那么你是說你沒有嗎
So you are saying that you did not?
不  女士  我沒有
No, ma'am. I did not.
你我都知道你插手了  州長
You and I both know that you interfered, Governor.
我私下問你的時候  你都承認了
You admitted so much to me when I asked you personally.
你跟我說將軍
You told me that the general
曾跟委員會的成員談過
had spoken to members of that committee.
我跟你說的是我在委員會有朋友
I told you that I have friends on the committee,
那是真的
which is true.
而不是我干涉了委員會的工作
Not that I interfere with committee work.
你讓每個共和黨人
You lined up every Republican
都反對俄羅斯入局
to be opposed to the Russians being involved.
他們都一致反對了
It was unanimous opposition.
如果你打算放棄鉆井
Well, if your plan was to get Russian support
以獲得俄羅斯的支持  我不怪他們
by giving away drill sites, I don't blame them.
那我們明確一下
So just to be absolutely clear, for the record,
州長  你是說
you are saying, Governor,
你本人或是將軍都沒有聯系過
that neither you nor the General made any contact
眾議院情報委員會的任何成員嗎
with any member of the House Intelligence Committee?
我絕對沒有
I absolutely did not.
你這是讓我左右為難
You're putting me in an impossible place here.
你偽造服役記錄時就將自己置于這種境地了
You put yourself there when you lied about your service record.
你想曝光誰的謊言
Whose lie do you want exposed?
康威的還是你自己的
Conway's or yours?
回家想一想
Go home and think about it.
不用趕在明天
Doesn't need to happen tomorrow.
只要在選舉日之前就行
It just needs to happen before Election Day.
我不是想抹煞你對于你丈夫
I'm not trying to diminish your contribution
總統工作的貢獻  安德伍德夫人
to your husband's presidency, Mrs. Underwood,
但我對你的經驗表示質疑
but I do question your experience.
沒有人在當上總統時
No one's fully prepared to be President
就充分準備好了
when he or she becomes one.
你也不能
Not even you.
看看民調結果
And look at the polls.
全國支持第一夫人做副總統的選民過半
Over half the country is open to a First Lady as VP.
想要一位新總統的選民也過半
And more than half of the country wants a new president.
你確實在民調中暫時領先  州長
It's true that you are leading in the polls for now, Governor,
但近幾周內  差距正在縮小
but the gap has been closing in recent weeks.
當人們前去投票
Well, when people show up to vote
不得不面對克萊爾·安德伍德
and have to confront the possibility
成為總統的可能性
of Claire Underwood as President,
他們就要摸摸良心  做出正確的選擇
they're gonna have a gut check and make the right choice.
說得非常對  那意味著他們會投給我們
You're absolutely right. That means they'll vote for us.
因為他們想想就會發現
Because they'll look around and realize
如果我出了什么事
that if anything happens to me,
他們能放心讓克萊爾接手
they'll be in very good hands with Claire.
而且她說得對
And, you know, she's right.
沒人能在做總統前完全準備好
No one can prepare to become the president.
而我已經是總統了
But I have been the President,
現在我知道那需要什么
and now I know what it takes.
需要的是信心  坦誠和效力
It requires confidence, openness, effectiveness,
而克萊爾具備所有這些品質
and Claire has all of those qualities.
很抱歉  總統先生
I'm sorry, Mr. President. It...
似乎我們得暫停一下
It looks like we have to take a break.
我們稍后將繼續進行史上首次
We'll return shortly to the first-ever simultaneous debate
總統候選人和競選搭檔的同場辯論
between presidential candidates and their running mates.
已停
And we're clear.
總統先生  安德伍德夫人
Mr. President, Mrs. Underwood,
兩位請跟我來一下好嗎
would you please come with me?
哈里發帝國組織
念出來
Read it.
什么
What?
"我們是美國公民
"We are citizens of the United States.
我們被哈里發帝國組織  以真主之名
We have been taken hostage in the name of God
作為人質扣押"
by the Islamic Caliphate Organization."
念出來
Read it.
"我們國家犯下了非法侵略
"Our country is guilty of illegal aggression
和大規模屠殺穆斯林的罪行
and mass murder against Muslims.
我們懇求寬恕"
We beg for mercy."
只有滿足以下要求  哈里發國才會給予寬恕
ICO will grant mercy only if these demands are met.
一  停止美軍在敘利亞的一切軍事行動
One, cessation of all U.S. Military activity in Syria.
二  向哈里發支付一百億美元賠償
Two, ten billion dollars in reparations paid to the Caliphate.
三  安全送還我們遭到
Three, the safe return of our leader,
不公正囚禁的領導人  尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪
Yusuf Al Ahmadi, from his unjust imprisonment.
我們不會和罪犯弗蘭克·安德伍德溝通
We will not communicate with the criminal Frank Underwood.
我們只和他的繼任者威廉·康威溝通
We will only communicate with his successor, William Conway.
如未能在24小時內滿足以上要求
If these demands aren't met in 24 hours...
將不予以寬恕
mercy will not be granted.
視頻在七個渠道上發布
Released to seven outlets.
通過加密郵件和暗網
Encrypted email, Deep Web.
三名人質是吉姆和卡洛琳·米勒夫婦
The hostages are Jim and Caroline Miller,
和女兒梅莉莎  是諾克斯維爾人
their daughter Melissa, from Knoxville.
總統先生  不論你需要什么
Mr. President, whatever you need,
我愿意提供幫助
I'm here to offer assistance.
我會告知你的
I'll let you know.
國土安全部
急事
我們目前識別出了板墻和照明設備
So far, we've identified the drywall and lighting.
都是美國制造的
All U.S. Manufactured.
視頻是用松下高清攝影機錄制
The video was shot on a Panasonic HD camcorder,
在美國銷量最大
most widely sold in the States.
所以可以確定他們在國內
So we know they're in the country.
民航班機可以排除
Well, commercial flight is out.
私人飛機不太可能
Private plane is unlikely.
我們很肯定他們是乘坐陸地交通
We're confident that they traveled by ground,
可能是米勒家被劫持的汽車
probably the Millers' hijacked car.
最后已知地點是諾克斯維爾市外一家丹尼餐廳
Last known location is a Denny's just outside of Knoxville.
一筆借記卡交易
A debit card transaction.
這是他們離開餐廳的影像
This is footage of them leaving the restaurant.
我們心系米勒一家人及其親友
Our hearts go out to the Millers' family and loved ones.
但我們相信總統
But we're confident that the President
正在盡一切可能營救他們
is doing everything possible to achieve their release.
我告訴總統  我們愿意
I told the President that we'd be willing
提供任何協助
to assist in any way if it would be helpful.
此時此刻美國必須團結一致并...
This is a time when America needs to pull together and...
暫停
Stop.
是"團結一致并為米勒一家人祈禱"
It's "pull together and pray for the Millers."
-然后再換我...  -我沒忘詞
- And then I come in, and-- - I didn't forget.
我只是認為這樣做不對
I just feel this is wrong.
此舉暗示我們愿意與恐怖分子談判
It implies we're willing to negotiate with terrorists.
我們該保持沉默
We should keep our mouths shut.
讓當權者去做他們的工作
Let the authorities do their job.
保持沉默不會為我們獲得新聞版面
We don't get press by keeping our mouths shut.
你已經讓我在全國節目上說謊
You had me lie on national television.
現在還要我們發布這種
And now you want us to send out some video
只會刺激恐怖分子的視頻
that only encourages these people?
而且這么做只為博得版面
And you wanna do that to score some press coverage?
如果你認為這么做不妥
If it doesn't make you feel comfortable,
我可以自己來
I can do it on my own.
我在外面等
I'll be outside.
我受夠他了
I've had enough of him.
他說的確實有道理
He does have a point.
無論我們是否發布這視頻
Look, they're gonna kill that family
他們都會殺害那一家人
whether we send this out or not.
我們還不如說我愿意盡義務出面
We might as well say I was willing to show up for duty.
我必須說  我同意將軍的看法
Well, I have to say, I agree with the General.
開始錄像
Press record.
Press record!
我們心系米勒一家人及其親友
Our hearts go out to the Millers' family and loved ones...
關于劫持者我們掌握了什么信息
What do we know about the captor?
我們敘利亞的線人說這是起單獨行動
Our Syrian assets say this is a lone wolf.
實際上  是兩人的行動
Two wolves, actually.
我們調高了視頻的對比度后
When we pumped up the contrast in the video,
在墻上發現了一個從攝影機后投射出的人影
we saw a shadow on the wall from someone behind the camera.
語音分析認為歹徒來自田納西州西孟菲斯地區
Voice analysis points to western Tennessee, Memphis area.
總統先生  我能說幾句嗎
Uh, Mr. President, if I may?
霍爾布魯克探員  我們的頂尖談判專家
Agent Holbrooke, our top negotiating expert.
我們針對這種事件進行過
Uh, we've run 16 possible models in preparation
16種情況模擬
for an incident like this.
目前的事件包含三種情況的關鍵因素
Now, what we have here are key elements from three of them.
美國綁架犯  兒童遭綁架
American kidnappers, the abduction of a child
以及要求溝通代理人
and proxy communication...
他們為什么指名康威
Why did they want Conway?
這才是重點  我告訴你為什么
That's the real question. I'll tell you why.
因為換做是我  我也會這么做
Because I would've done exactly the same thing if it had been me.
這能削弱我的權威
It undermines my authority.
讓我措手不及  挑起對立
Throws me off balance. Pits me against my rival.
還因為我沒有孩子  而康威有
And because I don't have children, and he does.
他們知道我不會妥協
They know I won't compromise.
沒有總統會妥協
No president would.
但康威這樣的總統候選人  或許會妥協
But a would-be president like Conway, well, he might.
戰術上我們需要更多時間
Tactically, we need more time.
我無法保證我們
I can't guarantee that we can
24小時內能追蹤到他們
track them down in less than 24 hours.
夠了  我的計劃是這樣的
Enough. Here's what I wanna do.
總統正與聯調局
The president is working with the FBI
及其他執法和情報部門合作
and other law enforcement and intelligence agencies
尋找米勒一家
to locate the Millers.
為了確保這些行動不受干擾
Now, in order to protect the integrity of those efforts,
我目前無法透露任何行動的具體進展
I won't be sharing any details on their progress at the moment.
同時  總統還尋求康威州長的支援
In the meantime, the president is reaching out to Governor Conway
為一旦與劫持者建立了聯系作準備
should contact with the captors be established.
有一點我要說清
Now, let me be clear.
這并不是談判
We're not talking about negotiation,
只是溝通
just communication.
你大可先私下問我
You could've asked me privately first.
這是戰略  向劫持者顯示
It was tactical, to show the kidnappers
我們尊重他們的要求
that we respect their wishes.
這讓我別無選擇
This doesn't leave me a choice.
你可以拒絕嘛  州長
Well, you can always say no, Governor.
我們已有一份計劃
We have a plan for how we can
即使沒有你的參與也能處理
handle this without your participation.
那要怎么進行
How would that work?
我會公開表示
Well, I say publicly that
我愿意親自與劫持者談
I'm willing to speak to the captors myself.
如果他們拒絕
Now, if they refuse,
我們得做最壞的打算
we'd have to be prepared for the worst.
但我們團隊相信
But our team believes that
有你在  我們建立對話的機會比較大
you give us a better shot at opening a dialogue.
好談判
To negotiate.
好為我們爭取時間
To buy us time.
如果你答應
And if you do say yes,
我們希望你盡快到白宮來
we'd want you at the White House as soon as possible.
我需要和我的團隊討論
I need to discuss with my people.
我希望你會同意協助我們
I'm hoping that you'll agree to help us.
無論如何  我盡快需要答復
Either way, I'll need an answer soon.
我了解  一小時內會給你回復
I understand. I'll let you know within the hour.
謝謝  州長
Thank you, Governor.
每個人都有缺點  而這就是康威的缺點
Everyone has a flaw, and this is Conway's.
我和總統談過  我說
I spoke with the president, and I said that
我愿提供任何協助
I'm willing to assist in any way if it would be helpful.
他渴望聚光燈
He aches for the spotlight.
否則他幾乎感覺自己是隱形的
He feels almost invisible without it.
如果他在這個舞臺的中央
Now, if he's center stage on this,
他就不能挑我的刺
he can't fault my performance,
因為我們要共享這個舞臺
because we're sharing the stage together.
如果我被喝倒彩  他就也被喝倒彩
If I get booed, he gets booed.
但康威渴望的其實是掌聲
But it's really the applause that Conway's hungry for.
相信我  他會同意的
Trust me, he'll say yes.
舞臺太大
The stage is too big
燈光太過誘人
and the spotlight too tempting
他受不了...僅僅當一個觀眾
for him to be... a mere spectator.
但我已經公開聲明如果他需要我會協助
But I've already said publicly I'd assist if he asked.
那是個錯誤
That was a mistake,
我應該更努力阻止的
and I should've pushed back on it more.
但你不能讓他利用你
But you can't let him take advantage of it.
我說都說了
Well, I've said it. It's done.
現在我們得往前走
And now we have to move forward.
這玩意真難喝
This is fucking disgusting.
你說  "經過慎重考慮
You say, "After much consideration,
我不愿意與恐怖分子談判"
I don't feel comfortable negotiating with terrorists."
那我不僅成了一個騙子
And then I come off not only as a liar,
還是個懦夫
but as a coward.
我們都領先了  為什么要這么做
Why do this when we're ahead?
領先多少  5個百分點  那不是領先
By what? Five points? That's not a lead.
是碰運氣
That's a coin toss.
整場競選我傳達的信息
My message this entire campaign
就是為國家服務  承擔責任
has been about serving the country, showing up for duty,
現在三軍統帥要我幫忙
and now I'm gonna not show up when the Commander-in-Chief
我卻拒絕嗎
has asked for my help?
...語言模式
...and the speech patterns.
劫持者是視頻中說話的人
The captor is the one who you heard on the camera.
似乎是美國人
Seems to be American.
從他公布視頻的方式可以看出來
And the way he's released the video shows
他是個電腦行家
he's computer savvy.
哈里發國招募人員已轉向使用社交網絡
Now, ICO recruiters have been turning to social media networks
比如臉書  推特  圖片分享
like Facebook, Twitter, Instagram,
和那些認同支持他們事業的用戶取得聯系
to initiate contact with users sympathetic to their cause.
-湯姆  -之前的組織  如基地組織
- Oh, Tom. - Earlier groups, like al-Qaeda,
使用社交網絡的程度
didn't use social networking
均遠遠不及哈里發國
anywhere near the degree that ICO has.
劫持者有可能...
It is possible that this captor...
-總統先生  -飛行順利嗎
- Mr. President. - Good flight?
-有點顛簸  不過還好  -進來吧
- A little bumpy, but fine. - Come on in.
你彈嗎
You play?
這個有待爭論
Well, that's debatable.
但我確實收集
But I definitely collect.
這是個大事
Uh, this is something.
是啊  太可怕了
Yeah, it's terrible.
我不羨慕此刻的弗蘭克
I don't envy Frank right now.
請坐
Have a seat.
-喝咖啡還是茶  -不用了  謝謝
- Coffee? Tea? - No, thanks.
發生了這么多事
I appreciate you taking the time,
我很感激你愿騰出時間見我
given everything that's going on.
反正又沒人打電話尋求我的建議
It's not as though anyone's calling for my advice.
但這篇文章目前似乎沒那么重要
Although I'm not sure this article is pertinent at the moment.
我不是來談你的獎學基金的
I'm not here about your scholarship fund.
我不明白了  我的助理說你想寫...
I don't understand. My assistant said you wanted to write--
我撒謊了...好讓你肯見我
I lied... so you'd meet with me.
我們有國內監控項目  處于調試階段
We have a domestic surveillance program, beta phase,
目標是找出哈里發國招募的人
aimed at finding ICO recruits.
外國情報監視法法庭裁決下來時我聽到了匯報
I was briefed when we got the FISA court ruling.
這是國內調查
Well, this is a domestic investigation.
我們必須通過聯調局工作
We have to work through the FBI.
他們準備派出一支隊伍
Now, they're sending over a team,
我希望國土安全部和中情局加入
and I'd like for Homeland and the CIA to join them.
這事很敏感  你不應該關起門辦事嗎
This is a sensitive program. Shouldn't you keep it in-house?
我們過去曾因不讓別的機構加入而受批評
We've been criticized for not involving other agencies in the past.
我想避免這個
I'd like to avoid that.
-你想要安全許可  -越快越好
- You want clearances? - As soon as possible.
事情緊急  需要齊心協力  道格
It's all hands on deck, Doug.
-州長  -總統先生
- Governor. - Mr. President.
這位一定是查理了
Well, and this must be Charlie.
-查理...  -和總統握手  查理
- Charlie... - Shake the President's hand, Charlie.
-來呀  查理  -你說他是個吸血鬼
- Come on, Charlie. - You said he was a vampire.
別擔心  你在這兒很安全
Well, don't worry. You're safe here.
白宮里沒有妖怪
No monsters in the White House.
我帶你們去住的地方
I'll show you where you're staying.
好的  走吧  查理
Okay. Come on, Charlie.
你去過總統辦公室嗎
Have you ever been in the Oval?
小時候去過一次
Once, when I was a kid.
童子軍  我們見了里根
My Boy Scout troop, we met with Reagan.
當然了
Of course they did.
我想你們會想住在一起
I thought you'd all like to be together,
所以安排在了這里
so I've put you in here,
如果不想  我們可以讓孩子住林肯臥室
but, if not, we can put the kids in the Lincoln Bedroom.
不用了  這兒太棒了  謝謝
No, this is wonderful. Thank you.
我們以后就要住這里嗎  媽媽
Is this where we're gonna live, Mommy?
那得看大選的結果了
We'll have to see how the election goes first.
有股臭味兒
Something smells.
天啊  莉莉需要換尿布了
Oh, gosh. Lily needs a change.
請問哪里有...
Um, where--
從這兒往右走就是衛生間
The restroom is here, to the right.
太好了  謝謝
Great, thank you.
你想讓我把一個共和黨人送進白宮
You want me to put a Republican in the White House.
你是想要一個共和黨  還是一個罪犯
You want a Republican or a criminal?
我對黨還是忠誠的  湯姆
I still have loyalty to my party, Tom.
那他們對你的忠誠呢
And where's their loyalty?
他們都打算彈劾你了
They were going to impeach you.
杰姬·夏普說服了民主黨
Jackie Sharp whipped Democrats.
你的國務卿也背棄了你
Your own Secretary of State turned her back.
你的黨  已經爛到核心了
Your party? It's rotten to the core.
而那個核心  就是安德伍德
And the core is Underwood.
他偷了你的總統之位你就不生氣嗎
Aren't you angry that he stole your presidency?
我當然生氣
I'm angry.
我氣我自己
I'm angry at myself...
沒能料到
for not seeing it.
還氣我沒和他斗到底
And for not fighting it.
那就現在反擊吧
So do something now.
我本來想說塔斯克撒謊了
I wanted to say Tusk lied.
但是得到特赦后  我知道沒人會相信我
But once I got the pardon, I knew nobody would believe me.
我就想
I thought...
"消失吧  躲得遠遠的"
"Just disappear. Go away."
而那種憤怒
And that anger...
如果我退隱了
If I went away...
那股怒氣也會消失
that anger would go away.
真相要曝光了
The truth is coming out.
一起來揭露吧
Be part of the truth.
民眾會相信你的
People will believe you.
等媒體發布會一結束  你的任務就完成了
Once we finish with the press conference, you'll be done.
后面交給我們就好
We'll take it from there.
如果他們聯系我們  你不需要我接電話嗎
You don't want me on the call if they contact us?
你的任務只是把他們引出來  州長
Oh, you're only there for bait, Governor.
我不能讓你代表白宮和他們談判
I can't have you speaking on behalf of the White House.
他們說了想和我交涉
They said they wanted me.
沒錯  但我們有計劃了
Yes, we have a roadmap in place.
那就調整一下吧
Then you'll have to adjust it.
你有什么資格大搖大擺走進來
What right do you have to walk in here
對我們的應對方案指手畫腳
and dictate how we're gonna handle this?
我來也是擔了風險的  這你知道
I put myself on the line coming here, and you know it.
我大可撒手不管  讓你自己焦頭爛額去
I could've backed off and left this pile of shit in your lap.
如果我要和你一起出鏡
Now, if I'm gonna be exposed with you,
那我對談判方案就得有發言權
then I'm gonna have some say in how that happens.
要不我就回紐約  看著你出丑
Or I head back to New York and watch you squirm.
正中我下懷
Just as I'd hoped.
他攙和得越深越好
The more involved, the better.
請接格林處長
Director Green, please.
他們來了嗎
They here?
-來了  -多謝
- They're here. - Thanks.
這是我們局長
This is our director.
-你好  -這是總統幕僚長
- Hello. - President's Chief of Staff.
我們需要過去三天內所有
We need every white male under 40
活動范圍不正常的40歲以下白人男性的資料
with geo-local anomalies in the past 72 hours.
已整理好了  也和你們的監視名單核對過了
Already done that, cross-referenced with your watchlists.
我們正在匹配電話語音
We're voice matching with phone calls now.
我們會派一支隊伍進駐
Well, we're bringing a team in here.
聯調局  中情局  國安部和我們的人
FBI, CIA, Homeland, along with our own people.
同時參與的人太多只會...
Uh, yeah, more cooks in the kitchen won't--
我已經給他們權限了
I've cleared them.
我們不能在溝通上耽誤時間
We can't waste time grapevining this.
讓大家坐在一起工作
Let's get everyone working from the same place.
我們需要組織工作流程
We need to organize workflow.
好  我們去我辦公室談
Right. Uh, let's talk in my office.
往右第二間就是
It's the second door on the right.
會有問題嗎
Is this going to be a problem?
我更希望他們不要監視我工作
I'd prefer them not breathing down my neck.
我問的不是這個
That wasn't my question.
我說了  都掩蓋好了
I told you, we're masked.
謝謝  請坐
Thank you. Please be seated.
我想感謝康威州長同意來協助我們
I'd like to thank Governor Conway for agreeing to assist us.
他和我的目標是一致的
He and I share the same goal,
就是讓米勒一家安全回家
which is the safe return of the Millers.
為實現這一目的
In order to achieve that,
我們將和劫持者
we're willing to open up lines
通過專線進行交涉
of communication with their captors.
州長
Governor.
我將作為你和總統之間的調解人
I will act as intermediary between you and the president.
想和我們聯系
To communicate with us,
只需依次撥打吉姆和卡洛琳·米勒的社保號
dial Jim Miller's social security number followed by Caroline's
使用任何手機或網絡運營商都可以
into any phone or Internet conferencing service.
然后將會有語音識別提示
There will be a voice recognition prompt.
讓米勒一家念出自己的名字和即時時間
Have all three Millers say their names and state the time
連線即會建立
and that will connect you.
我們心系米勒一家和他們的親屬
Our hearts are with the Millers and their families.
我昨晚和他們的親人通了話
I spoke to their siblings and their parents last night,
他們還在堅持著
and they remain strong.
我呼吁全體國民  為了他們  保持堅強
And I would ask all Americans to remain strong on their behalf.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
易卜拉欣·哈拉比  美穆關系協會會長
雖然眼下情勢非常險惡
Deplorable as this situation is,
但我們不能怪罪全體伊斯蘭人士
we cannot blame Islam as a whole
也不應牽連國內渴望和平的數百萬穆斯林
or the millions of Muslims in our nation who yearn for peace,
他們為我們的社會辛勤奉獻
who contribute to our society,
和所有美國人共享一個美國夢
who have the same dreams as all Americans do.
哈里發國不能代表伊斯蘭
ICO does not represent Islam.
但是某些別有用心的人會利用這次事件
But there are those who would use this incident
為采取強硬措施尋找借口
to justify draconian measures,
比如出行限制或強制注冊等
like travel restrictions or forced registration,
他們這是在鼓吹仇恨  甚至暴力
who would espouse hatred or even violence.
一旦愛國走上了偏執的歧路
The moment bigotry becomes a form of patriotism,
美國就不再是美國了
America is no longer America.
所以我今天來到國會
That is why I'm here today, in the Capitol,
呼吁各位眾議員
to urge our congressmen and women...
聽說有人支持籌贖金
Hear there's a push to get the ten billion.
財政委員會吵翻了天
Big debate in Ways and Means,
但是絕對到不了眾議院表決
but it'll never make it to the floor.
裝裝樣子而已
It's just for show.
我一直在和撥款委員會談
I've been with Appropriations.
-想繞過財政委嗎  -不是
- Bypass Ways and Means? - No.
為向敘利亞派地面部隊增兵作撥款準備
To pay for more ground troops in Syria if we need them.
那為什么約我來這里  而不是在國會
So why are you meeting me instead of at the Capitol?
湯姆·漢默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
他也聯系你了嗎
Has he called you, too?
聯系了  但我什么都沒說
He reached out, but I haven't said a word.
沃克公開聲明了
Walker went on record.
告訴他是我發動本黨議員彈劾他
Told him I was the one who whipped the votes for impeachment.
你的說辭就是你認為他有罪
Your story is you thought he was guilty.
這沒什么不對的
There's nothing wrong with that.
這么說你和他談過了
So you have talked to him?
他有幾個推論
He has some theories.
我只是把他想錯的地方澄清了
All I did was shake my head at the parts that weren't right.
你不開口  就不會擔責任
You're clean if you don't talk.
我想開口  接受他采訪
I want to. On the record.
我認為你也該這樣
I think you should, too.
我們不行
We can't.
那些照片一泄露  你的眾議員席位就不保了
You will lose your seat as soon as those photos are leaked.
反正也快保不住了
I may lose my seat anyway.
康威的超級政治行動委員會
Conway's super PAC is targeting
在針對所有選情嚴峻的加州民主黨參選人
every California Democrat in a tight race.
就算我贏了  國會也是共和黨占多數
Even if I win, I'm in a Republican-controlled Congress
總統也是共和黨人
with a Republican president...
要不就是再給安德伍德當四年走狗
or I have to do Underwood's bidding for the next four years.
那艾倫呢
What about Alan?
我把我們的事告訴他了
I told him about us.
他挺大度的
He was kind about it.
等事情消停了  我們就離婚
We'll divorce once everything quiets down.
如果你不希望照片流出  那我不開口就是了
If you don't want the photos out there, I won't say anything.
我不在乎全世界怎么議論我
I don't care about what the rest of the world thinks of me.
我只想保護你
All I cared about was protecting you.
那我們站出來吧  雷米
Then let's do this, Remy.
只要我們站出來  他就完了
You and I go on the record, he's done.
約書亞·馬斯特森  田州理工計算科學專業
Joshua Masterson. Computer science major at Tennessee Tech.
過去兩年一直熱衷于研究
Taken a keen interest in Islamic studies
和伊斯蘭教有關的事
during the past two years.
連續翹課三天
Hasn't been to class in three days.
也沒有與親友聯系
None of his friends or family have heard from him.
他的聲音和視頻里的匹配
Voice matches the one in the video.
我們判斷他的同伙是扎克瑞·霍松
We believe his associate is Zachary Hawthorne,
高中輟學  和馬斯特森關系很近
high school dropout who's remained close with Masterson.
上周二開始翹班
Stopped showing up for work last Tuesday.
等他們打來  我應該...
So if they call, should I...
我要表明我們知道他們的身份嗎
should I tell them that we know who they are?
不  你只要自我介紹就行  州長
No, you'll introduce yourself, Governor,
然后介紹我來接手對話
then you introduce me.
不  讓州長和他們交涉
No, the governor will do the talking,
他到底能不能用他們的名字
so should he use their names or not?
這可能會刺激他們做出沖動之舉
It could cause them to do something rash.
瑪奇探員是我們的首席心理學家
Agent March, our head psychologist.
所以我不能提
So I shouldn't.
但反過來說  這或許能使他們回歸常人
Conversely, it could humanize them.
消除匿名給他們的信心
Removes the confidence of anonymity.
但如果他們因此逃跑  那就壞事了
But if they run, it compromises everything.
不止如此  我們確信這就是他們的身份
Not just that. We're confident on the IDs,
但還是有極微小的可能猜錯了人
but if there's the slightest chance we're wrong,
那就會削弱我們在談判中的地位
it weakens our position.
那電話里先別提他們的名字了
Then don't use their names in the call.
先生  我們的對話腳本
Uh, sir, our script is written
是以我作為交涉人撰寫的
with the understanding that I'd be speaking.
我們還需要為州長重新調整
We'd have to rework it for the governor.
那馬上進行調整
Well, then let's rework it now.
我們不知道他們什么時候會打來
We don't know when they'll be calling.
雖然現在的情況很糟糕
You know, the circumstances are awful,
但我還是得承認
but I have to admit...
能從競選中解脫一小會兒真是太棒了
it's been nice to take a break from the road.
我不知道你是怎么做到的
I don't know how you do it,
同時當競選搭檔和第一夫人
running mate and First Lady.
事實上我自己也在琢磨呢
I'm still trying to figure that out myself, actually.
我覺得這令人敬佩
I think it's admirable.
如果我們贏了
If we win,
我想做點更新圖片分享之外的事
I'd love to do something more than update my Instagram.
我當時批評那個  只是...
When I criticized that, it was just because--
不  沒關系  我不介意
No, not at all. I didn't take offense.
這是政治
It's politics.
我想做點類似你槍支法案那樣的事
I'd love to do something like your gun bill.
沒能通過參議院真是遺憾
It's a shame it didn't pass the Senate.
你支持那項立法
You support that legislation?
我來自英格蘭
Mmm, I'm from England.
我們認為你們對槍支的癡迷太瘋狂了
We think your gun obsession is madness.
威爾也是  但是他不能承認
Will does, too, but he can't admit it.
-不能惹怒中堅選民  -對呀  中堅選民
- Mustn't upset the base. - Ah, yes, the base.
不能惹怒中堅選民
Mustn't upset the base.
你其實是我的榜樣
You know, you're actually a role model of mine.
你做的那些工作  環保
I mean, your work on the environment,
性侵犯  當大使...
sexual assault, being ambassador...
當然了  我更想我們贏
I mean, obviously, I'd prefer if we win.
但如果贏不了
But if we didn't,
你一定能成為一名優秀的副總統
I think you'd make a wonderful Vice President.
媽媽  你在喝什么
Mommy, what are you drinking?
是咖啡  親愛的
It's coffee, sweetheart.
我也想要  我也想要
I want some! I want some!
別這么大聲  會吵醒妹妹的
Not so loud. You'll wake your sister.
我能喝一點嗎
Can I have some?
你還太小了
You're not old enough.
你想喝水嗎  或是果汁
But do you want some water or some juice?
冰箱里應該有果汁
I think we've got some juice in the fridge.
我去拿
I'll get it.
他好可愛
He's very cute.
你后悔沒要孩子嗎
Do you regret it, not having children?
對不起  這個問題太私人了
Oh, I'm sorry. That's too personal.
那你后悔過要孩子嗎
Do you ever regret having them?
聲音已經確認了  他們在線上  先生
We've got voice verification. They're on the line, sir.
我需要拖住他們好讓你們追蹤通話嗎
Do I need to keep them engaged so you can trace the call?
不用  是網絡通話
No, Internet call.
每30毫秒換路由  無法追蹤
Rerouted every three milliseconds. Untraceable.
我們有兩個主要目標
We have two main objectives.
獲取更多信息  拖延最后期限
More information, extending the deadline.
但最重要的是證明人質還活著
But our top priority is a first concession. Proof of life.
所以你什么都別承諾
So you'll promise nothing.
好
Okay.
記住他們可能會對通話錄音
Keep in mind that they may be recording this call.
他們想要炒作
It's publicity they want.
好  我準備好了
Okay, I'm ready.
我是康威州長
This is Governor Conway.
我想和吉姆  卡洛琳和梅莉莎通話
I'd like to speak with Jim, Caroline and Melissa.
你和我說
You speak to me.
我需要證據證明他們還活著
I need some proof that they're still alive.
請告訴梅莉莎她的祖父母非常想念她
Please tell Melissa that her grandparents miss her very much
他們在為她祈禱
and, uh, they are praying for her.
你這么做不會讓我們為他們感到抱歉
You're not gonna make us feel sorry for 'em.
你向無辜的穆斯林
How sorry did you feel
投炸彈的時候  又有多抱歉  州長
when you dropped bombs on innocent Muslims, Governor?
總統是個懦夫  派別人去替他殺人
The President's a coward. He sends others to do his killing.
但你更壞
But you're worse.
你還發表講話說你對打了一場不義之戰
You make speeches about how proud you are
名字?
感到多么的自豪
that you fought in an unjust war.
如果炸彈落在你女兒身上  你會是什么感受
How would you feel if a bomb was dropped on your daughter?
如果她被炸飛  死無全尸
If she was blown up and had to be buried in pieces?
你是美國人  對嗎
You're American, right?
我們效忠于尤瑟夫·艾哈邁迪
Our allegiance is to Yusuf Al Ahmadi
和哈里發帝國
and the Islamic Caliphate.
美國是我們的敵人  必須滿足我們的要求
America is our enemy and must meet our demands.
你知道
Uh, you understand that
我不能代表政府說話
I can't speak on behalf of the government.
我只能把你說的話轉達給總統
I can only communicate what you say to the President.
我需要些時間
I'll need some time.
你當我們傻嗎  他正聽著呢
You think we're stupid? He's listening right now.
我是總統
This is the President speaking.
我們只和康威說話
We talk to Conway only.
如果你想要什么的話
But if you want anything to happen,
只有我能辦到
I'm the one that can make it so.
那你為什么什么都不做
Then why have you done nothing?
我在和國會討論贖金的事
I'm talking to Congress about the money.
和我的軍事顧問討論撤軍
I'm consulting with my military advisers about a pullout,
但這些都不可能在幾小時內完成
but nothing can happen in a few hours.
你就是想拖延時間好找到我們
You just want more time so you can find us.
我們在找你們嗎  是的
Are we looking for you? Yes.
只是為保證你們把米勒一家毫發無傷地交出來
But that's only so you'll turn over the Millers without incident.
不會有什么移交
But there is no handing over.
要么滿足我們的要求  否則他們就得死
Either you give us what we want or we kill them.
不證明他們還活著  我們什么都不會做
Nothing will happen until we have proof of life.
好吧  給你個活著的證據
All right, here's your proof of life.
把那女孩舌頭割了
Cut out the girl's tongue.
-不  -我是康威
- No! - This is Conway.
-不  -請不要沖動
- No! - Please, before you do anything...
-媽媽  -約書  扎克
- Mommy! - Josh. Zach.
你以為我們在乎你知道我們的身份嗎
Do you think we care you know who we are?
不  住手
No, stop!
我想跟你談談  一小會兒就行
I'd like to speak with you, just for a moment.
我有話要說
I... I have something to say,
但別讓梅莉莎再叫了
but I need Melissa to stop screaming
-這樣我才能聽清你  -不
- so I can hear you. - No!
我能聽聽她說話嗎
Can I hear her voice?
我們必須聽見她說話
We need her voice.
我在這兒  我是梅莉莎
I'm here. I'm Melissa.
你好  梅莉莎  我是威爾
Hi, Melissa. My name is Will--
你聽見她說話了  快說吧
You heard her voice. Now talk.
不
Oh, no.
對  我殺過很多人
Yes, I... I've killed a lot of people.
其中有無辜者
Some of them innocent people.
每一晚
And every single night...
我都沒對我妻子說過
I haven't even told my wife this...
但每一晚  我都做噩夢
but every single night, I have nightmares.
我想象我自己的女兒  莉莉
I picture my own daughter, Lily,
我的妻子  兒子
and my wife... and my son,
就像你說的那樣
just like you described...
被炸飛
blown away.
死了
Gone.
你可以說我
Now, you could say that I...
我做噩夢是因為我做得不對
I have these demons because what I did was wrong
而你的動機是正義的
and that your cause is righteous.
但我當時也認為我的動機是正義的
But I believed that my cause was righteous, too.
如果能撤銷發生的事
And if I could take it all back...
我不會做同樣的事
I wouldn't do it again.
其實
The truth is...
我為我的行為感到羞恥
I'm ashamed of what I've done.
總統說得對
Now, the president is right.
我們需要更多時間來籌備你們的要求
We need more time to work on your demands,
但更重要的是
but more importantly,
我猜你之前從沒殺過人
I'm guessing you've never killed anyone before.
身為一個了解殺戮的人  我要說
And speaking as someone who knows what it means to kill,
在做出無法挽回之事前
you owe yourselves more time
你該給自己更多時間
before you do something you can never take back.
約書
Josh?
早九點  你們的最后期限
9:00 a.m. You have till then.
他們結束通話了
They've ended the call.
你做得非常好  州長
You did an excellent job, Governor.
謝謝
Thank you.
我們有一通戰況室電話的錄音
We have a recording of the Situation Room call
是由劫持者在不久前放出的
released by the captors a short while ago.
在播放音頻之前  我們想提醒聽眾們
Before playing this audio, we want to warn viewers
其中部分內容會令人不安
that there are sections that are very disturbing.
肯尼迪總統遇刺
林登·約翰遜宣誓就職
建議大家把電視靜音
You might want to mute the television.
人都哪去了
Where is everybody?
他們都去忙劫持的報導了
They all got pulled on the hostage story.
把他們叫回來
Get 'em back here.
還有瑪姬·蒂爾頓
And Maggie Tilden, too.
轉錄  馬上做
Transcribe this, right away.
查塔努加市外方圓50英里范圍內
Fifty mile radius outside of Chattanooga.
用偷來的信用卡買汽油
Gas purchase on a stolen credit card.
馬斯特森的同學之一
One of Masterson's classmates.
我們現在要放出他們的照片嗎
Should we just release their photographs at this point?
我的電話被打爆了
I'm getting bombarded with calls.
州長用的是名字
Well, the governor used the first names.
會有人把線索拼湊起來的
Someone's gonna put it together.
-我們不如利用這一點  -先生
- We might as well exploit it. - Sir.
-喬治  -總統先生
- George. - Mr. President.
通常  我會給你時間重新考慮
Normally, I'd give you time to reconsider,
但今天時間太緊
but time is in short supply today.
不行  我不能這么對黨派
I can't. Not to my party.
黨會撐下去的
The party will survive.
康威也許不能  沒辦法  他撒謊了
Conway might not, but too bad. He lied.
如果我這么對他  我就撐不過去了
If I do this to him, I don't survive.
我會被鄙視
I'm vilified.
我想給你看點東西
I wanna show you something.
你知道這是什么嗎
Do you know what this is?
這是我做黨鞭時
This is your magnet
喬·沃勒克
你在投票記數板上的磁鐵名牌
from the vote count board when I used to be whip.
喬·沃勒克
曾有很多次
There were so many times when
你不在我希望你在的位置  喬治
you weren't in the column I wanted you to be in, George.
我們都知道  我那時有幾十次
And we both know that I could've forced you
可以逼你按照我的意愿投票
to vote the way I wanted you to dozens of times,
但我從沒那么做過  我克制住了
but I never did. I held back.
是為了保護你的名譽
To protect your honor.
做黨鞭的好處之一
And one of the advantages of being whip
就是每個黨員
is that behind every single member,
每塊磁鐵名牌之后
behind all of these magnets,
都至少有一件不光彩的事
was at least one dishonorable thing.
只不過你的事恰好比大多數人都更不光彩
Yours just happens to be more dishonorable than most.
所以這次我要把你放在我那一欄里  喬治
So I'm putting you in my column this time, George.
莉安告訴我你在這兒
LeAnn told me you were in here.
我在寫你的聲明
I'm working on your statements,
為最壞的情況做準備
in case the worst happens.
真是緊張  這個地方
It's tense, this building.
墻壁里都透著這氣息
You can feel it in the walls.
我早些時候去散步
I went for a walk earlier.
空氣里都彌漫著緊張
It was in the air.
人們交談都輕聲低語
People were talking in whispers,
雖然完全沒有必要這樣
even though there was no reason to.
要不就兩眼盯著手機
Or their eyes are glued to their phones.
沒有孩子在外面玩耍
And there are no children out...
一個都沒有
anywhere.
我想稱之為恐怖是有原因的
I guess they call it terror for a reason.
比恐怖更糟  是恐懼
Worse than terror. Dread.
人們因一場悲劇把自己束縛起來
People girding themselves for a tragedy.
也可能反過來
Mmm, and it could go the other way.
你怎么樣
How are you holding up?
漢娜在照看她的孩子
Hannah is minding her children.
我在照看她
I'm minding her.
她丈夫的表現真是出色  是吧
Her husband really knocked it out of the ballpark, huh?
你覺得他說的是真心的嗎
Do you think anything he says is genuine?
這不重要  不是嗎
Doesn't matter, does it?
起作用了就好
It worked.
你曾經說你覺得康威只會表面功夫
You said once you thought he was all surface, Conway.
是啊  自戀狂
Yeah, a narcissist.
但如果給他一灘水照照自己
But give him a pool to reflect in...
就要當心了
Watch out.
該怎么做  他清楚得很
He knows exactly what to do with that.
除非他弄巧成拙
Unless he overreaches.
你就希望如此嗎
Is that what you were hoping?
希望他把這事搞砸嗎
That he was gonna fuck it up?
因為他不會搞砸的
Because he's not gonna fuck it up.
他太聰明了
He's too smart for that.
"他升到空中
"There he soared,
從大本鐘和倫敦眼旁邊呼嘯而過
zipping past Big Ben and the London Eye,
又從白金漢宮和皮卡迪利廣場上方飛過
over Buckingham Palace and Piccadilly Circus.
看  他遠去了"
Look at him go."
我馬上回來  查理
I'll be right back, Charlie.
守夜的氣氛特別陰沉
... the vigil is especially somber,
但上午早些時候達成的延期
but there remains a great deal of hope
還是帶來了不少希望
after the deadline was extended earlier this morning.
-很多人將延期歸功于州長  -情況如何
- Many credit that extension to Governor... - What's the latest?
有進展  搜索范圍縮小了
Progress. They've narrowed the search zone.
通話中  可以聽見梅莉莎在尖叫
During the call, Melissa could be heard screaming
因為馬斯特森讓霍松"割掉..."
as Masterson orders Hawthorne to, quote, "Cut out..."
水槽左邊
Left of the sink.
此時康威州長介入
That's when Governor Conway stepped in.
抱歉  你也來一瓶嗎
Oh, I'm sorry. You want one?
不了  謝謝
No, thank you.
現在我們播放他說的部分內容
We're going to play some of what he said right now.
-因為你的肝嗎  -對  我...
- Is it your liver? - Yes, I...
-保持清醒  -我殺過很多人
- Clear mind. - I've killed a lot of people.
其中有無辜者
Some of them innocent people.
每一晚...
And every--
為什么關掉
Oh, why'd you turn it off?
我當時就在旁邊
I was there.
一定讓你很抓狂吧
That's gotta drive you crazy, huh?
我這下要有多少正面報道了
How much good press I'm getting out of this.
-什么這么好笑  -沒什么
- What's funny? - Nothing.
告訴我吧  我也想聽笑話
Come on, tell me. I want in on the joke.
你以為你能激怒我
You think you can get under my skin.
我們第一次見面時  我就激怒你了
Oh, I got under your skin the first time we met.
什么時候  新年前夜嗎
When? New Year's?
我記得我那晚恭維了你
I believe I complimented you that night.
但你盡可以
But you go ahead,
為了擺出更高的姿態
you tell yourself what you have to
自欺欺人
in order to stand a little taller.
我真為你難過
I feel sorry for you.
兩年
Two years.
你只能待這么點時間
That's all you're gonna get in here.
你在任的時間不會比沃克長
You're not gonna last any longer than Walker did.
最讓你難受的  是我會做個了不起的總統
And what kills you is that I'll make a great president.
真正會被銘記的總統
The kind of president who'll actually be remembered.
那不是比死還讓你難受嗎  弗蘭克
And isn't that worse than dying, Frank?
被遺忘
Being forgotten.
你還真以為你會是個了不起的總統
You actually think you'd make a great president.
今天只是小試牛刀
Today was just a little taste.
總統99%的工作是不為人知的
99% of this job is in the dark.
你今天在陽光下閃耀了一會兒
I mean, you had your little moment in the sun today,
但當你要做無數個
but what are you gonna do
永遠無人知曉  無人感激的決定時
when you have to make a thousand decisions that no one will
你要怎么辦呢
ever hear about or appreciate?
我覺得你很擅長競選總統
I think you're excellent at running for the president,
但我不認為你真有能力做總統
but I don't think you're equipped to actually be one.
別這么居高臨下
Don't be condescending.
我是紐約州長
I'm the Governor of New York.
奧爾巴尼  是嗎
Ooh, Albany, really?
你是個冒牌貨  威爾
You're a pretender, Will.
而如果你贏了
And if you win,
你就從冒牌貨成了騙子
you'll go from pretender to fraud.
威爾
Will?
我要讓孩子們睡覺了
I'm putting the kids to bed.
那我不耽擱你了
Don't let me keep you.
-也許你該送他們回家  -還不到時候
- Maybe you should send them home. - No, not yet.
除了沃勒克還有別的打算嗎
Do you have something else in mind besides Walleck?
有  而且我需要你幫我
Yes, and I'll need your help.
查理  你看見他了嗎
Charlie? Have you seen him?
查理
Charlie?
媽媽  你看我找到了什么
Mommy, look what I found!
快瞧瞧
Oh, look at those.
還給我  你不能玩這個
Give those back. Those aren't yours to play with.
-我能留著嗎  -快還回去  查理
- Can I keep them? - Oh, um, hand them over, Charlie.
-查爾斯  -要不這樣吧
- Charles. - No, you know what?
你還是留著吧
You should keep them,
因為你這一生就應該順心如意
because you should get everything you want in this life.
快說謝謝
Um, say thank you.
-謝謝你  -應該謝謝你才是
- Thank you. - No, thank you
多謝你來白宮看我們
for coming to the White House to visit us.
我們都休息吧  明早七點見
We should get some rest. I'll see you at 7:00.
那時候我早就起了
Oh, I'll be up way before then.
-晚安  -晚安
- Good night. - Good night.
晚安
Good night.
我怎么幫你
You need my help how?
-還有誰知道  -沒人了
- Who else knows about this? - No one.
我需要你盡快安排
I'll need you to make arrangements as quietly as possible.
好  我去辦
All right, I'm on it.
我拿到地址之后馬上告訴你
I'll let you know as soon as I have a location.
好  回家睡幾個小時吧
Good. Then go home and get a few hours of sleep.
我今晚可睡不著
I can't sleep tonight.
試試吧  我們需要你明早精力充足
You should try. We'll need you fresh in the morning.
-聯系參聯會主席  -好的
- Get me the Chairman Joint Chiefs. - Yes, sir.
勞拉·莫雷蒂
他在線上了  先生
He's on the line, sir.
主席先生
Mr. Chairman.
你想什么時候聯系白宮
When do you wanna reach out to the White House?
明天  郵件我已經寫好了
Tomorrow. I've drafted the email.
-你已經檢查過了嗎  -是的
- You looked this over? - Yes.
法律上我們沒有問題
We're okay on the legal front.
但我們不該等人質危機結束嗎
But shouldn't we wait until this crisis is over first?
絕不  這是我們的絕佳機會
No. This is perfect timing for us.
湯姆說得對  趁他不備  攻他不意
Tom's right. Let's hit him while he's distracted.
怎么樣
How is it?
很好吃
Perfect.
你冰箱里實在是沒什么可做的
Well, you didn't have much to work with in your fridge.
你得去買點吃的了
You need to do some grocery shopping.
-我不常做飯  -看出來了
- I don't cook a lot. - Obviously.
你需要的話就回去照顧孩子吧
If you have to get back to your kids...
沒事
No, it's fine.
哈莉16歲了  有需要的話她會打給我的
Haley's 16. She'll call me if she needs anything.
他們看新聞了嗎
Have they been watching the news?
看了  他們嚇壞了
Yeah... and they're freaked out by it.
誰不怕呢  但是他們現在承受能力強多了
I mean, who isn't? But they've got thick skin by now.
比他們的同齡伙伴們鎮靜多了
Handling it a lot better than some of their friends.
我知道有好多父母
I know a lot of parents aren't
明天甚至都不打算讓孩子出門了
even letting their kids out of the house tomorrow.
連學也不上了
Not even to go to school.
不過我的孩子還是會去的
My kids are gonna go, though.
我不會讓這些畜生毀了我們的生活
I'm not gonna let these monsters rule over our lives.
-多謝你過來  -客氣
- Thanks for coming over. - Of course.
我就算躺床上也只會盯著天花板發呆
I know I'd just be staring at the ceiling if I tried to sleep.
你的工作太繁重了
Well, you have a lot on your shoulders.
一般我會去參加個互助會什么的
Yeah, normally, I'd go to a meeting.
我只是...
I... I just, uh...
你只是希望能有人照顧你
You just wanted someone to take care of you.
能照顧別人也挺好的
And it's nice to take care of someone.
早上好  州長
Good morning, Governor.
你的電話
Your phone.
喂
Hello?
我們拍到一輛車
We have video of a car
在佐治亞州查茨沃思附近一十字路口處
at an intersection near Chatsworth, Georgia.
電話背景音里有鳥叫聲
The bird song, deep background from the phone call,
說明他們在林區  南藍嶺
puts them in a wooded area. Southern Blue Ridge.
我們已經開始搜索了
We started canvassing now.
聯調局  州警
FBI, state troopers.
電話連線了
The line is open.
好的  我的對話腳本呢
Uh, okay. Where... where's my script?
我來交涉
I'll be doing the talking.
需要你加入的時候我再告訴你
I'll let you know if I want you to participate.
先生  如果綁匪和州長之間
Sir, if we've established a dialogue
已經建立了對話  那我們應該...
between the kidnappers and the governor, we should--
接通吧
Start the call.
■
與人們印象中的"不與恐怖分子談判"不同
美國政府處理人質綁架事件的原則實際上是
"不妥協  不讓步"
就是說  美國政府未必不會與恐怖分子或恐怖組織
就人質問題進行協商
2015年6月  奧巴馬政府通過總統行政命令的形式
進一步修改和明確了相關政策
允許美國政府官員代表人質家屬同綁架者進行協商
但是法律仍然規定  美國政府不會向綁架者支付贖金
很多時候  "談判"的界限在這種協商和交流中被模糊
有時候  美國政府也會為特定人質的獲釋付出很大代價
■
最近的一則例子  發生在2016年1月
三名美國公民在伊拉克被綁架
經調查  綁架者為當地什葉派軍事武裝人員
背后有伊朗支持
事發后  美國政府向伊拉克政府尋求幫助
在伊拉克情報機構和軍方的斡旋下
三名人質于一個月后被釋放
美國政府稱  在尋求人質釋放的過程中
他們沒有直接同綁架者接觸
但具體的談判過程  綁架者是否得到贖金  外界不得而知
■
另一樁引起廣泛關注的綁架案  涉及一名美國現役軍人
2009年  美軍士兵鮑爾·伯格道在阿富汗前線失蹤
后確認被塔利班綁架
美軍曾經組織多次營救行動  但均未成功
有特種兵戰士在營救任務中陣亡
經過美國政府同塔利班的長期談判
2014年5月31日  伯格道被塔利班釋放
美國總統奧巴馬親自在白宮宣布了這一消息
作為交換  美國釋放了五名被關押在關塔那摩監獄的塔利班囚犯
據媒體報道  這五名囚犯被俘前均在塔利班武裝中擔任重要職務
■
伯格道獲釋后  他的一些戰友向媒體透露
他是擅自離開前線后被塔利班俘獲的  是一名逃兵
部分美國國會成員和媒體對奧巴馬政府
用五名高危恐怖分子換取一名"逃兵"的行為非常不滿
白宮因此承受了很大壓力
目前伯格道因叛逃罪正在接受軍事法庭的審判